# Zepeng Chen My portfolios &

#### About me a bit

I was an electronics engineer in China mainly focusing on embedded hardware system and sometimes assisting software team in writing drivers of MCU and FPGA. After three years of professional work, I moved to Australia as a backpacker working in farm, hotel, restaurant and meat factory for one and half years; and then I moved to Canada for working on the master's degree of computer engineering.



zepengchen423@gmail.com



(709)327-7352



St. John's, Canada



zepengblog.herokuapp.com

in

linkedin.com/in/zepchen



github.com/zepsgit

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript HTML CSS

React JSON REST API

Express Nodejs Java

Python MongoDB

Database SQL Git

Web Development

Machine Learning

Data Analysis Matlab

Skilearn Pandas Numpy

OpenCV

# **LANGUAGES**

#### **English**

Full professional Proficiency

#### Chinese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Coding

Basketball

Reading

Calligraphy

Travelling

## **Work Experience**

### **Electronics Engineer**

#### Alpha Networks Inc.

06/2016 - 05/2019

Chengdu, China

- Designed the schematics and layouts of PCB.
- Wrote driver of Flash memory and implemented the communication protocol between MCU and peripheral devices.
- Followed up mass production of an amount of 10k with the reject ratio under 0.5%.

### **Academic & Personal Projects**

## Personal Blog (03/2022 - 06/2022) [2]

- Implemented the front-end pages using React, JSX, CSS.
- Connected server to **MongoDB** using **Mongoose**.
- Fetched and sent data via Axios.
- Designed routing with Express.

### Marine Mammal Sound Classification (01/2022 - 06/2022) 2

- Fetched audio data, and built metadata for all audio files for machine learning and deep learning.
- Used Python, Pandas, Librosa, and Scikit-Learn in Jupyter Notebook to build machine learning models.
- Explored and learned different algorithms of machine learning and deep learning, and used **Keras** and **Tensorflow** to implement deep learning models.

## Optical Music Recognition (05/2021 - 09/2021) &

- Implemented several image pre-processing algorithms such as image filtering, binarization, and segmentation using **Python.**
- Employed **OpenCV** and **CNN** for image classification.

#### **Education**

# **Master of Applied Science in Computer Engineering**

#### Memorial University of Newfoundland

05/2021 - 09/2022

■ GPA: 3.6/4.0

St. John's, Canada

# **Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics Engineering**

# Hubei University of Technology

09/2012 - 06/2016

Wuhan, China

■ GPA: 3.0/4.0